{
    "subject": "resource/Churchill_Gunasekara",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Colombo",
    "human_readable": "Churchill Gunasekara was born in Colombo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9307277202606201,
            "question": "Where was Churchill Gunasekara born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5943834781646729,
            "question": "What other notable people were born in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40835681557655334,
            "question": "Is there a museum dedicated to people born in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18608689308166504,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the history of Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18385055661201477,
            "question": "Is Colombo a city in Sri Lanka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17518819868564606,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16525185108184814,
            "question": "What are some famous landmarks in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11200115829706192,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10925322026014328,
            "question": "Are there any festivals celebrated in Colombo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06871096789836884,
            "question": "What are some popular foods from Colombo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Churchill Gunasekara was born in Colombo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_482_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any festivals celebrated in Colombo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_482_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Colombo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_482_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some famous landmarks in Colombo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_482_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_482_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is explicitly stated that:\n\n\"Churchill Gunasekara, commonly known as Churchill, is a renowned Sri Lankan celebrity who has made his mark in the fields of entertainment, arts, and politics. Born on July 12, 1951, in Colombo, Sri Lanka...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided, which states that Churchill Gunasekara was \"Born on July 12, 1951, in Colombo, Sri Lanka.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}